Mr. Pei.
Sorry.
How is he?
How is it?
The next two days are critical.
Fortunately, you rescued him in time.
Otherwise,
the old man would be gone.
As long as he's fine.
Sorry to trouble you.
Why did Grandpa faint so suddenly?
I don't know either.
When I just got back,
Grandpa was already lying on the floor.
What have you been busy with these past two days?
Weren't you at home?
What do you mean, Brother?
Do you think
I didn't take good care of Grandpa?
I didn't mean that.
I was just asking.
Since you haven't been at the company for the past two days,
I was curious about what you were up to.
Do you have a girlfriend now?
No.
Jingyan is here.
How is Grandpa?
The doctor says he is out of danger,
but he needs to be observed for another two days.
That's good.
I was scared to death.
Pei Song.
Pei Song,
it really is you.
Is there any problem with
the big data analysis system you created?
Shiya,
are you doubting me?
Does the volunteer registration post for the
big data analysis experiment online
have anything to do with you?
Why did you tell me to stay away from Pei Ning?
And what do you mean by saying you are reborn?
Who exactly are you?
Why do you know all my preferences,
as if you've known me for a long time?
Shiya,
put the knife down first.
Answer my question first.
I can only tell you
that I will absolutely not hurt you.
What exactly were you doing there tonight?
I am also investigating
that registration post for the big data analysis experiment.
Why?
I suspect someone wants to use
the big data analysis experiment system
to steal personal privacy.
The simplest one,
fraud.
Just copy the code he wrote into this USB drive,
and that's it.
So,
you suspect it's Pei Ning?
I can't be sure right now
what he is plotting.
What do you mean?
What do you mean
by 'right now'?
Shiya,
are you willing to believe me?
I...
It's okay.
You don't have to believe me,
but remember one thing.
I will never hurt you,
ever.
Pei Song,
should I believe you?
Shiya,
give me a little more time.
I will find out everything.
I suspect this is a fake IP address.
Could it be encrypted?
Look.
You just think the encryption method of this code
is very similar to Morse code.
The key is the codebook.
It's the same principle as sending a telegram.